Ninja Hattori-kun + Perman:
ESPer wars
Look forward to Heroics of Hattori-kun and Perman at New York!
Now in theaters.
Set in New York, Hattori's ninja art and Perman's powers combine into one.
Wow, amazing!
Damn you, Kemumaki...!
Ken-chan, keep it up! That's the spirit!!
Show him!
Alright, just you wait and watch!...
Bluff while you still can.
How interesting!
That's weird!
Watch where you fly!
Maybe my controller broke.
You did that on purpose.
Please help me!
Who is she?
I'm being chased. Please help me!
How cute!
Have no fear when I'm here for you. No worries.
Huh? Who are those guys?
Weird guys are coming here, Ken-chan.
Alright! I'll take you on.
Who are you guys? If you lay your hand on her, I won't ever forgive you!
Let go of her.
Alright, I'll handle them!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Hands up!
Hattori-kun!
Elder brother!
Alright, in that case, I'll use this ninja flute!
Oh my! I'm shy.
Wait, someone's calling me.
Shinzō and others must have got into some kind of trouble.
I must go!
Ninja Hattori-kun + Perman:
ESPer Wars
Ah, that's Ken'ichi and co. What happened to them?
Wait, I said.
What are you planning to do with that girl?
I'll get rid of you!
Ninja art of !
Nice!
Ninja art of Paralysis, binding hand and foot!
Lady Shibame, now's the time.
Don't drop her.
Who is it? Show yourself!
Hand over that girl peacefully.
Who are you?
That outfit, so you're Hattori-kun, a ninja.
Not just Hattori, my full name is Hattori Kanzō.
Will your ninja arts work against me, Psycho-man?
Your name is Psycho-man, you say?
He can float in the sky.
He can move and fly also?
Without even using any ninja techniques?!
You're surprised at only this much, you have lot of homework to do
Psycho-beam!
Watch out!
Are you alright, Hattori-kun?
Thanks for saving us.
Peryan!
Pako, take care of Hattori-kun and others.
Here we go!
Is that you, Perman?
Psycho teleportation!
Ouch!
I don't have time to play tag with you.
That voice...
Ah, elder brother!
Let's use Shin-chan's ninja art of crying!
3.. 2... 1... Go!
Huh? What is this power?
Shinzō!
Run!
Where did he disappear?
You're right!
As long as we have Shin-chan's crying power, we have nothing to fear!
It's alright now.
Thank you!
My name is... Yuri.
You came to Japan from Paris, only to get in such a scary situation.
What do your parents do back at France?
You came all alone?
"I came from Africa", he says.
I don't want to know anything about you.
My mum passed away 3 years ago.
When I was small, my parents got divorced.
My brother lived with my father, and I lived with my mother.
But I'm not in contact with my father or brother.
Is that so?
So Yuri-chan, you're looking for your father and brother?
Yes.
I feel sorry for her.
But then, who is this Psycho-man who's after you?
I have absolutely no idea.
All of you must be hungry, it's now lunch-time!
I want yakisoba!
Too bad. I've only prepared curry today.
Looks yum!
Excuse me... I want to help...
You're welcome to.
But since you're our guest, leave it to us.
Aunty, this plate right?
Yes!
Mum, is curry done yet?
What?
This is amazing even compared to our ninja art.
It's Telekinesis.
Lady Yuri, what kind of training have you taken?
I have taken no such training.
But I've been able to perform more and more since then.
It's a mysterious force that is yet to be explained by science, right?
Saikou-man, here we are at your service.
You fools! Don't make me repeat myself!
Note: Saikou means Best.
It's not Saikou-man but Psycho-man!
Yes, Saikou-man.
You have to retrieve Yuri at all costs, who's the most prominent ESPer.
That ninja kid Shinzo is an Expert psychokinetic.
But boss...
Pardon us, but what are you trying to do by obtaining ESPers?
Is that the only question that comes to your head?
Listen, the young ESPers.
At present their power is less. However, with time in training they become powerful ESPers.
We will weaponise the ESPers.
Gather all ESPers and unleash them upon the world.
We shall dominate the world. The entire world shall belong to me and my dad.
Ok, I understand. Yuri-chan, leave it to us.
Right, Hattori-kun, Perman?
From tomorrow, we all will search for Yuri-chan's father and brother!
Good idea!
Thank you. But tomorrow...
Tomorrow's Sunday.
We have day off, let's all search.
So you're going to appear on that show?
Yes.
I'll lead you to TV station.
It's be all for the naught if something were to happen to you.
Let's all send Yuri-chan.
Yep, leave it to me.
Yup.
The World